deepweb-sites.com 2019-03-24

# Privacy and Cookie policy - Deep Web

**Effective date** : 22th of May 2018

_Your privacy is important to us. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully_

  1. ### Introduction

We collect certain personal data from the individual user (“you” and “your”) through the website <https://www.deepweb-sites.com/> (the “Website”). This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) contains our policies and procedures governing the collection and processing of personal data through the Website.

**Definitions.** For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, the term “personal data” refers to any information relating to a natural person who can be identified, directly or indirectly, by using such information, and the term “processing” refers to the collection, storage, erasure, use, and disclosure of personal data.

**Data controller.** The entity responsible for collection and processing of your personal data is Deep Web Sites.

**Term and termination.** This Privacy Policy enters into force on the effective date indicated at the top of the Privacy Policy and remains valid until terminated or updated by us.

  2. ### Your Consent

By using the Website, you acknowledge that you have read this Privacy Policy and you agree to be bound by it. You agree to the collection of your personal data for the specified, explicit, and legitimate purposes described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not understand or do not agree with one or more provisions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website.

We will seek your explicit consent in advance if we would like to:

  * Use your personal data for any purposes that are not explicitly indicated in this Privacy Policy;
  * Provide you with any marketing communication;
  * Transfer your personal data to third parties that are not indicated in this Privacy Policy; or
  * Make significant amendments to this Privacy Policy.

  3. ### Types of personal data collected by us

We comply with data minimization rules and collect only a minimal amount of personal data that is necessary for ensuring your proper use of the Website:

  * When you visit the Website, we collect your IP address;
  * When you contact us by using the contact form available on the Website, we collect your (i) name, (ii) email, (iii) website (optional), and (iv) any other information that you decide to provide us in your message;
  * When you submit a comment under the blog posts, articles, news, and instructions featured on the Website or create a profile on the Webiste, we collect your (i) name or nickname, (ii) email address, (iii) website (optional), and (iv) any other information that you may decide to provide us.

**Sensitive data**. We will not collect, under any circumstances, any sensitive data from you, such as your health information, opinion about your religious and political beliefs, racial origins, membership of a professional or trade association, or information about your sexual orientation.

  4. ### The purpose of personal data

We respect data protection principles and we collect your personal data only for specified, explicit, and legitimate purposes. The personal data collected through the Website is used only for:

  * Providing you with the services requested by you, answering your questions, and responding to your requests;
  * Verifying your contact details;
  * Ensuring the proper functioning of the Website;
  * Customizing Website’s content based on your location;
  * Sending you important notifications about the Website; and
  * Audit and security purposes.

Our legal ground for the collection of your personal data is pursuing our legitimate business interests. We will not use your personal data for purposes that are different than the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy unless we obtain your prior express consent.

  5. ### Non-personal data collected by us

When you visit the Website, we may collect non-personal data, such as your browser types, operating systems, and URL addresses of websites clicked to and from the Website. We will collect such non-personal data in order to analyze what kind of users visit the Website, how they find it, how long they stay, from which other websites they come to the Website, what pages they look at, and to which other websites they go from the Website.

  6. ### Marketing communication

We WILL NOT send you any direct marketing communication, including newsletters, brochures, and advertisements, or contact you by phone or in any other manner, unless you provide us with your prior explicit consent to receive such marketing communication.

**Opt-out from marketing communication.** In case you have provided us with your explicit consent to receive marketing communication, you can opt-out from receiving it at any time by:

  * Clicking on the “unsubscribe” link contained in any of our marketing emails sent to you; or
  * Contacting us directly at [contact@deepweb-sites.com](mailto:contact@deepweb-sites.com).

  7. ### Protection of personal data

We employ organizational and technical security measures, such as limited access to your personal data by our staff, secured networks, pseudonymization, and encryption, to protect your personal data. However, please note that, due to the inherent risks of using the Internet, we cannot be liable for any destruction, loss, leakage, and falsification of personal data caused by circumstances beyond our reasonable control. We will put reasonable efforts to maintain the security of and to prevent misuse, loss, unauthorized access, and modification of your personal data. We kindly ask you to use only secure networks for communicating with us.

  8. ### Third party access to personal data

In certain situations, we may disclose your personal data to third parties. Such a disclosure is limited to the situations when your personal data is required for the purposes of (i) provision of the services requested by you, (ii) pursuing our legitimate business interests, (iii) law enforcement purposes, or (iv) if you provide your prior explicit consent. For example, your personal data may be disclosed to third parties that (i) provide services on behalf of us or (ii) provide us with technical support, such as:

  * Our information logistics providers (e.g., [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/));
  * Our push notification provider [OneSignal](https://onesignal.com/); and
  * Other parties who assist us in operating the Website and conducting our business.

The third parties will access your personal data as a part of their partnership with us and only if such third parties agree to assure an adequate level of protection of your personal data that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. With the exceptions mentioned in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose your personal data to third parties, unless we are legally bound to do so.

**Your comments.** Please note that the comments submitted by you under the blog posts, articles, news, and instructions featured on the Website may be visible and accessible to other users of the Website. Please be sensible in disclosing any personal information about you or any third parties through the comments.

  9. ### Transfer of personal data outside the EEA

Please note that some third parties indicated in this Privacy Policy may be located outside of the jurisdiction in which you reside and, if you are a resident of the EEA, your personal data may be transferred outside the EEA. In case it is necessary to make such a transfer of your personal data, we will ensure that the jurisdiction in which the recipient third party is located ensures an adequate level of protection of your personal data or we conclude an agreement with the respective third party that ensures such protection.

  10. ### Your rights regarding your personal data

You have the possibility to exercise the following rights regarding your personal data:

  * You can ask us to **access, modify, move, or delete your personal data**. We may ask you to provide us with an identifying piece of data, so that we would be able to identify you in our system;
  * You can ask us to **object or restrict the processing of your personal data** (e.g., stop sending you marketing communication);
  * If you have provided us with your explicit consent, you have the right to **withdraw such consent** at any time;
  * If you would like to **launch a complaint** about the way in which your personal data is handled, please contact us first. After you contact us, we will send you a confirmation that we have received your complaint. Afterward, we will investigate your complaint and provide you with our response within a reasonable timeframe but no later than 2 weeks. If you are a resident of the EU and you are not satisfied with the outcome of your complaint, you have the right to lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority.

If you would like to exercise your rights listed above, please contact us by using the contact details indicated in section 16 “Contact us”. We will answer your request as soon as possible but no later than 2 weeks.

  11. ### Retention Period

Your personal data will be kept by us only for as long as it is necessary for the purpose for which such personal data was collected. When your personal data is no longer necessary, we will delete your personal data immediately, unless we are required by law to retain such personal data.

  12. ### Children’s privacy

According to the Terms and Conditions of the Website available at <https://www.deepweb-sites.com/terms-and-conditions/>, the Website cannot be accessed and used by persons under the age of 13. However, we cannot distinguish the age of people accessing the Website. If a person under the age of 18 has provided us with personal data without obtaining parental or guardian consent in advance, the parent or guardian may contact us and request us to destroy such personal data. Our contact details are specified in section 16 “Contact us” of this Privacy Policy.

  13. ### Third-party links

The Website may contain links to other websites (e.g., social media service providers). We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third-party websites and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them. Please read carefully the privacy policies of the third-party websites before submitting any personal data to them.

  14. ### Cookies

The Website uses cookies. By using the Website, you agree to our use of cookies as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our use of cookies, please refuse cookies. Below, you can find more information about what cookies we use, for what purposes we do so, and how to refuse cookies.

**What is a cookie?**

A cookie is a small computer file. It typically consists of letters and numbers. When you visit a website, the website may send a cookie to your browser. Subsequently, the browser may store the cookie on your computer system. The main purpose of cookies is to allow a website to recognize user’s device. There are two types of cookies, namely, persistent cookies and session cookies. Persistent cookies remain valid until their expiration date, unless deleted by the user before that date. Session cookies will be stored on a web browser and will remain valid until the moment when the browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain personal data. However, personal data stored by us may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. Web servers can use cookies to (1) identify and track users while they navigate through different pages on a website; and (2) identify users returning to a website.

**What cookies do we use?**

We use both session and persistent cookies. We use session cookies, such as [“gads”, “ga”], in order to verify your details until you are navigating from page to page on the Website. The session cookies enable you to avoid re-entering your details each time you enter a new page on the Website. We use persistent cookies, such as [“gid”, “cfduid”], in order to recognize you as a unique user when you return to the Website. We will not use cookies for purposes, which are not mentioned in this Privacy Policy.

**Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics to analyze your use of the Website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about the Website by means of cookies. The information generated by Google Analytics in relation to the Website is used to create reports about the use of the Website. We use the following Google Analytics advertising features: (i) Remarketing with Google Analytics; (ii) Google Display Network Impression Reporting; (iii) Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting; and (iv) Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data via advertising cookies and identifiers.

If you would like to opt out from Google Analytics advertising features, you can do so through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (for example, the NAI’s consumer opt-out). You can also install a Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

**Third-party ads**

Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to the Website. Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve you ads based on your visits to the Website and/or other websites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of personalized advertising by visiting <https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated>. Alternatively, you may look for more information on how to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/consumers>.

Third-party vendors that are certified by Google for third-party ads may serve ads on the Website. The names of such third party-vendors and links to their websites can be found at <https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/94149?hl=en>. You may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for personalized advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability).

**How to refuse cookies?**

If you do not agree to our use of cookies, you need to either (i) discontinue your use of the Website or (ii) set your browser to refuse cookies. If you would like to refuse our use of cookies, you can do so by checking your browser’s “help” information or visiting [http://www.whatarecookies.com](http://www.whatarecookies.com/) for further information. Please be aware that some parts of the Website may not function properly without cookies.

  15. ### Amendment of this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting an amended version on the Website. Your continued use of the Website after posting such an amended version will constitute your acknowledgment of the amendments and your consent to abide and be bound by the amended Privacy Policy. If we make significant amendments of the Privacy Policy, we will seek your explicit consent to the amendments.

**Last amendment.** This Privacy Policy has been last amended on 22th of May 2018.

  16. ### Contact details

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by:

  * **Email:** [contact@deepweb-sites.com](mailto:contact@deepweb-sites.com)
  * **Contact form:**  <https://www.deepweb-sites.com/contact-us/>
